1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications 6347 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications
1982-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
1199SEIU Rochester
SEIU 1199 Upstate
1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East
Service Employees International Union
SEIU Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.)
6347 PUBS
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Publications.
9219309
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
9219309
- Directory of Local Unions 2003-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Directory of Local Unions, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Rochester and Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation, AFL-CIO
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Directory of Local Unions, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Directory of Local Unions, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Directory of Local Unions, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Directory of Local Unions, 2012-1013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Directory of Local Unions, 2012-1013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2.
- 1199 Constitution and By-Laws 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: 1199SEIU
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 2: Constitution, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: District 1199 Rochester and Upstate New York Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, SEIU
  - Item 4: By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Local 1199Upstate, SEIU
- SEIU Constitution and By-Laws 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: SEIU 2000 Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: SEIU
  - Item 2: SEIU 2000 Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rochester Labor Council Constitution and By-Laws 1991, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO
- SEIU 1199 Upstate in the News Fall 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: SEIU 1199Upstate In the News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Collected news clippings Fall 2000
- SEIU Institute on the News March/May 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: SEIU 1199Upstate In the News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Collected news clippings March-May 2001
- SEIU 1199 Upstate in the News June/September 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: SEIU 1199Upstate In the News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Collected news clippings June-September 2001
- SEIU 1199 Upstate in the News October/November 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: SEIU 1199Upstate In the News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Collected news clippings October-November 2001
- SEIU 1199 Upstate in the News June/August 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: SEIU 1199Upstate In the News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Collected news clippings June-August 2002
- Healthcare Worker Update 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Update, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Healthcare Division of SEIU
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1987:Fall)
  - Item 2: Update, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1988:Winter)
  - Item 3: Update, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1988:Spring)
  - Item 4: Update, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1989:Winter)
  - Item 5: Update, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1989:Winter/Spring)
  - Item 6: Healthcare Worker Update, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1991:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 7: Healthcare Worker Update, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1992:Winter/Spring)
  - Item 8: Convetion '92 Update, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Special Issue (1992:Spring)
  - Item 9: Convetion '92 Update, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Special Issue (1992:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Healthcare Worker Update, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1992:Summer)
  - Item 11: Healthcare Worker Update, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1993:Winter/Spring)
  - Item 12: Healthcare Worker Update, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1993:Summer)
  - Item 13: Healthcare Worker Update, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1993:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 14: Healthcare Worker Update, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1994:Winter/Spring)
  - Item 15: Healthcare Worker Update, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1994:Summer)
  - Item 16: Healthcare Worker Update, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1994:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 17: Healthcare Worker Update, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1995:Summer)
  - Item 18: Healthcare Worker Update, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1995:Fall/Winter)
- SEIU Action 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: SEIU Action, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (2001:June/July)
  - Item 2: SEIU Action, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (2001:October)
  - Item 3: SEIU Action, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (2001:November/December)
  - Item 4: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2002:January/February)
  - Item 5: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2002:May/June)
  - Item 6: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2002:July/August)
  - Item 7: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (2002:September)
  - Item 8: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (2002:October/November)
  - Item 9: SEIU Action, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (2002:December)
- SEIU Action 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1998:January)
  - Item 2: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1998:February/March)
  - Item 3: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1998:April)
  - Item 4: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1998:May)
  - Item 5: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1998:June)
  - Item 6: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1998:July)
  - Item 7: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1998:August)
  - Item 8: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1998:September)
  - Item 9: SEIU Action, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1998:October)
  - Item 10: SEIU Action, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2000:Convention Issue)
  - Item 11: SEIU Action, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (2000:June/July)
  - Item 12: SEIU Action, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (2000:October)
  - Item 13: SEIU Action, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (2000:November)
- SEIU Action 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: SEIU Leadership Action, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: Fall 1996.
  - Item 2: SEIU Leadership Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: March/April 1997.
  - Item 3: SEIU Leadership Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: March/April 1997. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: SEIU Leadership Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 1997.
  - Item 5: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1997:June)
  - Item 6: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1997:July)
  - Item 7: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1997:August)
  - Item 8: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1997:September)
  - Item 9: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1997:October)
  - Item 10: SEIU Action, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1997;November/December)
- Service Employees Union 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Service Employees Union, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1991:Winter)
  - Item 2: Service Employees Union, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1991:Spring)
  - Item 3: Service Employees Union, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1992:Winter)
  - Item 4: Service Employees Union, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1993:Summer)
  - Item 5: Service Employees Union, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1993:Fall)
  - Item 6: Service Employees Union, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1994:Winter)
  - Item 7: Service Employees Union, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1995:March/April)
  - Item 8: Service Employees Union, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.9:no.5 (1995:December)
  - Item 9: Service Employees Union, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1996:Spring)
- Services Employees Union 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Service Employees Union, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1987:September/October)
  - Item 2: Service Employees Union, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1987:November/December)
  - Item 3: Service Employees Union, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1988:January/February)
  - Item 4: Service Employees Union, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1988:March/April)
  - Item 5: Service Employees Union, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1988:May/June)
  - Item 6: Service Employees Union, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1988:September)
  - Item 7: Service Employees Union, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1988:October/November)
  - Item 8: Service Employees Union, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1989:February/March)
  - Item 9: Service Employees Union, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1989:April/May)
  - Item 10: Service Employees Union, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1989:June/July)
  - Item 11: Service Employees Union, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1989:August/September)
- Our Life and Times 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Our Life and Times, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (2006:November)
  - Item 2: Our Life and Times, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (2007:January)
  - Item 3: Our Life and Times, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (2007:December)
- The Monitor 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Monitor: Professional and Technical Newsletter, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 2009.
  - Item 2: The Monitor: Professional and Technical Newsletter, 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: February 2011.
  - Item 3: The Monitor: Professional and Technical Newsletter, 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 2011.
  - Item 4: The Monitor: Professional and Technical Newsletter, 2012; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: June 2012.
- Delegates 1199 SEIU 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Delegates, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (2003:June)
  - Item 2: Delegates, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (2003:September)
- Local 1199 Upstate News 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: Winter 2002.
  - Item 2: News: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: July 2002.
  - Item 3: News: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: October 2002.
  - Item 4: News: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: October 2002. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: News: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 2003.
  - Item 6: News: The Voice of Health Care Workers in Upstate New York, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 2003. Copy 2.
- 1199 SEIU Captain Region News 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Capital Region News: Newsletter for the 1199 SEIU Capital Region Division, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: July 2003.
- 1199 SEIU New Jersey News 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: New Jersey News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (2003:Spring)
- 1199 SEIU Plan of Work 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: 1199 SEIU Plan of Work, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: December 2002 to April 2005
- SEIU President's Committee 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Report 1 Summary: Evaluate, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: SEIU President's Committee 2000
    Notes: SEIU's progress and the changing world around us
  - Item 2: Report 2: Imagine, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: SEIU's opportunies to change the future
- SEIU Cooks, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: SEIU Cooks!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: Gift Catalog
  - Item 2: SEIU Cooks!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: Gift Catalog. Copy 2.
- Wade Norwood 2005, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Wade Norwood for Rochester Mayor, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: Campaign flyer
  - Item 2: Plan for Progress: Wade Norwood for Mayor, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Author: Friends of Wade Norwood
- 2003 Annual Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: 2003 Annual Review: Our Voice, Our Vision, Our Funds, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: Employment, Training and Job Security Program
  - Item 2: 2003 Annual Review: Our Voice, Our Vision, Our Funds, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: Employment, Training and Job Security Program. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 2003 Annual Review: Our Voice, Our Vision, Our Funds, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: Child Cate Fund
- 1199 SEIU National Benefit Fund 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: National Benefit Fund for Rochester Area Members, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Author: 1199SEIU National Benefit Fund
    Notes: Summary Plan Description
  - Item 2: Your Benefits, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
- League/ 1199 SEIU Training and Upgrade Fund 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Training and Upgrade Fund, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Author: League 1199SEIU
    Notes: Plan Document
- Stronger Together in SEIU 1199 Upstate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: SEIU Local 200A, the AFL-CIO Hospital and Nursing Home Council, SEIU 1199 Rochester, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: Stronger Together, In SEIU 1199Upstate
  - Item 2: SEIU Local 200A, the AFL-CIO Hospital and Nursing Home Council, SEIU 1199 Rochester, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: Stronger Together, In SEIU 1199Upstate. Copy 2.
- Assault on the Job 1995, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Assault On The Job: We Can Do Something About Workplace Violence, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: 2nd edition
- A New Voice for SEIU Members 1996, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Many Voices, One Union: A New Voice For SEIU Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: SEIU Committee on the Future
    Notes: Report 5 from the SEIU Committee on the Future
- A Vision of Change for America 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: A Vision of Change for America: President Clinton's Budget Proposal, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: SEIU Department of Public Policy
    Notes: Fiscal Year 1994 Federal Budget: Impact on SEIU Members and the States
- Paying More and Losing Ground, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Paying More and Losing Ground: How Empolyer Cost-Shifting Is Eroding Health Coverage of Working Families, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: AFL-CIO
- Celebrate Moe! 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Celebrate Moe!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: Honoring 1199's Voice for Justice
- Why Roses With Our Bread?, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Why Roses With Our Bread?, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Author: Esther Cohen
    Notes: Reprint from New Labor Forum (2001:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 2: Why Roses With Our Bread?, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: Reprint from New Labor Forum (2001:Fall/Winter). Copy 2.
- One New York 2006, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: One New York: An Agenda For Shared Prosperity, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Author: Fiscal Policy Institute
    Notes: Discussion Paper, November 2006.
- 1 Year of Bald Action 1996, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: 1 Year of Bold Action, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Social Justice Calendar 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Social Justice Calendar 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Author: Bread and Roses Cultural Project; SEIU Greenhouse Cultural Program
  - Item 2: Social Justice Calendar 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- One Statewide Health Care Union 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Stronger Together! One Statewide Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Author: 1199SEIU; Local 1199Upstate, SEIU
  - Item 2: Stronger Together! One Statewide Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: One Statewide Health Care Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: One Statewide Health Care Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Now's Our Chance to Help Build New York's Biggest, Strongest Health Care Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 6: Now's Our Chance to Help Build New York's Biggest, Strongest Health Care Union, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- University of Rochester/ Strong Memorial Hospital, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Respect Worker Free Choice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: SEIU Local 200United
  - Item 2: Respect Worker Free Choice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: 5 Paychechs from Poverty!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: SEIU Local 200United; SEIU Local 1199
  - Item 4: Please Tell UR: "Don't Take My Healthcare!", Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 5: A Tale of 2 Universities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: A Tale of 2 Universities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 7: A Tale of 2 Universities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Copy 3.
  - Item 8: Jobs Justice and Health Care March for Respect, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 9: Jobs Justice and Health Care March for Respect, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Healthcare Education Project 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Healthcare Education Project Rally and March, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: April 1, 2003. Albany, NY. Collection of news clippings.
- Testimony of SEIU 1199 Upstate Members 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Testimony of SEIU 1199Upstate Members: Public Hearing on Nursing Home Quality of Care, Staffing and Regulations, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Notes: January 31, 2001. New York State Assembly Committee on Health and Committee on Aging
- Better Care, Better Uses, 2014; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Better Care, Better Lives: The Affordable Care Act at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: SEIU Healthcare
- The Power on Purple 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The Power of Purple: SEIU Poetry Jam, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Notes: 23 poems by SEIU members
  - Item 2: The Power of Purple: SEIU Poetry Jam, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Notes: 23 poems by SEIU members. Copy 2.
- Community Support for Episcopal Church Home Employee Organizing 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Community Support for Episcopal Church Home Employee Organizing, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Author: Episcopal Church Home Organizing Committee
- 1199 SEIU Flyers, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Rochester's Healthcare Workers and Families: Hang On To Your Hard-Earned Dollars!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 2: Rochester's Healthcare Workers and Families: Hang On To Your Hard-Earned Dollars!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 3: 1199SEIU National Benefit Fund for Rochester Area Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: The United Members of 1199 SEIU Helped Save Our Children's Hospital, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 5: The United Members of 1199 SEIU Helped Save Our Children's Hospital, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 6: "I didn't know my Union could help me get a bigger tax refund", Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 7: Working together, we helped save our Children's Hospital, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 8: Working together, we helped save our Children's Hospital, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 9: The Road We Have Traveled: A History of 1199SEIU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 10: The Road We Have Traveled: A History of 1199SEIU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 11: We Are The Members of SEIU, Local 1199Upstate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 12: We Are The Members of SEIU, Local 1199Upstate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 13: We Are The Members of SEIU, Local 1199Upstate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 14: Finger Lakes Occupational Health Services, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Author: University of Rochester; Finger Lakes Occupational Health Services
  - Item 15: Health Care Workers Score Huge Win in Albany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 16: Health Care Workers Score Huge Win in Albany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 17: Strike! The Real Deal, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 18: Let's Keep Political Action Working of Rochester Families, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 19: SEIU Sronger Together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Unions and Upward Mobility for Women Workers 2008, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Unions and Upward Mobility for Women Workers, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Author: John Schmitt
    Notes: December 2008.
- News Clippings, 1997-2012 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Unionize Everybody!, 2011; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Michael I. Niman
    Notes: v.10:no.11 (2011, March 17)
  - Item 2: On he anniversary of Martin Luther King Jr.'s death, a call to make joining a union a civil right, 2012; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Richard Kahlenberg; Moshe Z. Marvit